tetrain.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Tetra Website

**Introduction**

We, at 'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' and our affiliated companies worldwide, are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. In order to provide a personalised browsing experience, Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd. may collect information from you, this may include technical or other related information from the device used to access Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd. including without limitation contact lists in your device and its location, you may also be asked to complete a registration form. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your end. 

"Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.'s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about activity on the web site. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. 

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the web site. 

Tracking technologies may record information such as internet domain and host names; internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics. 

**Third Party Services**

Third parties provide certain services available on www.Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd. on Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.'s behalf. 'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' may provide information, including Personal Information, that 'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' collects on the web to third-party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information, and services. Service providers are also an important means by which 'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' maintains its web sites and mailing lists. 'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.'s behalf. 

'Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.' does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.'s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Tetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd.'s policy to sell Personal Information collectedTetra Information Services Pvt. Ltd. online without consent.
